[♪♪]
I'm Peppa Pig.
This is my little brother,
George.
[SNORTS]
This is Mommy Pig.
And this is Daddy Pig.
[SNORTS]
[ALL LAUGH]
Peppa Pig.
[GRUNTS]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and her friends
are at their playgroup.
Today we are going
to make a time capsule.
[SNORTS]
What's a time capsule?
A time capsule is something that
will show people in the future
how we lived.
How?
We'll put special things
in this box,
and then we'll bury it
in the school garden.
Will it grow?
[ALL LAUGH]
MADAME GAZELLE:
No, Suzy.
It will remain in the ground
for many years.
ALL:
Ooh!
Now, what things
should we put inside?
[SNORTS]
A comic.
Very good, Peppa.
[BLEATS]
Music.
Very good, Suzy.
[BARKS]
A toy.
[NEIGHS]
A coin.
[WHINNIES]
Stamps.
[SQUEAKS]
A carrot?
[LAUGHS]
MADAME GAZELLE:
You do like carrots,
don't you, Rebecca?
Yes.
[ALL LAUGH]
All those are excellent things
to show our daily lives.
Madame Gazelle,
what will the future be like?
MADAME GAZELLE:
What do you think
it will be like?
I think in the future
I will live on the moon.
[GIGGLES]
And all my friends
will come to visit.
[ALL LAUGH]
[BARKS]
And I will fly
a space rocket.
Hello.
[ALL LAUGH]
Now we'll record a message
for the people of the future.
Say hello
to the future.
Hello to the future.
You're probably
all living on the moon now.
And going on holiday
to Mars.
And flying around
in space rockets.
[ALL LAUGH]
Wonderful.
It is nearly home time,
and all the parents
have arrived.
Mommy, Daddy, we've made
a time capsule.
Ah, Daddy Pig.
You're just in time
to help us dig a hole.
Yes, of course.
Daddy Pig is digging
a hole in the school garden,
for the time capsule.
There.
Can we dig it up now?
[LAUGHS]
It will remain in the ground
for many years.
Oh, but I can't wait
that long.
Peppa, you are just like your
Daddy was when he was little.
Am I?
Yes, I remember
when I was his teacher.
Did you teach
my Daddy?
Yes. I taught all of your
mommies and daddies, didn't I?
ALL:
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
[ALL LAUGH]
When your mommies
and daddies were little,
they made a time capsule too.
Yes, we did. We buried it
next to a little tree.
Can we dig it up?
Yes. I think we buried it
over here.
Oh. I thought it was
a much smaller tree.
Oh, it was
a long time ago.
The tree has grown a bit
since then.
[ALL LAUGH]
[METALLIC THUMP]
I've found something.
It's our old
time capsule.
ALL:
Hooray!
I can't wait to open it.
[ALL LAUGH]
Stand back, children.
ALL:
Yes, Madame Gazelle.
And what do we have here?
Oh, an old comic.
That was my
favorite comic.
A tin toy.
My favorite toy.
Music.
My favorite record.
And a very old carrot.
That's mine.
What a good choice,
Mommy.
[ALL LAUGH]
And a videotape
of your mommies and daddies
when they were little.
ALL:
Ooh.
[GIGGLES]
Who's the little piggy
in the glasses?
MOMMY PIG:
Oh, that's Daddy Pig.
Oh. And that's me.
Hello to the future.
[GIGGLES AND SNORTS]
What a squeaky voice
you have.
[CHUCKLES]
You're probably living
on the moon now.
Silly little Daddy Pig.
[ALL LAUGH]
NARRATOR:
Making time capsules
is such fun,
and finding them
is even better.
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Peppa and George
are going to the seaside
with Granny and Grandpa Pig.
[HORN HONKS]
[BOTH GIGGLE]
Peppa and George
love the seaside.
Oh. Where's the sand gone?
There isn't any sand
on this beach, Peppa.
No sand?
But we wanted
to make sand castles.
Peppa and George
love making sand castles.
[SOBS]
Now now, George,
don't be upset.
There are lots
of exciting things to do
on this rocky beach.
Like what?
GRANDPA PIG:
When the sea goes out,
it leaves little pools
of water in amongst the rocks.
They're called
rock pools.
GRANDPA PIG:
And in every rock pool,
there's something special
that the sea has left behind.
Ooh. I can see something
glittering.
It's a coin.
Wow.
Maybe it's a pirate's
treasure?
ALL: Ooh.
[SNORTS]
Let's make a collection
of all the things we find.
Yes. We'll put them
in George's bucket.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
What surprise
is waiting in this pool?
There's nothing special
in this one.
[LAUGHS AND SNORTS]
There's always
something, Peppa.
Look closer.
Ooh, there is something.
Yes, it's a crab.
Aah!
The crab is pinching
Grandpa Pig's finger.
Oh!
Ouch.
[SNORTS]
Naughty Mr. Crab.
[LAUGHS]
Look, George.
Mr. Crab
is walking sideways.
[GIGGLES]
George is pretending to be a
crab.
Peppa wants
to be a crab too.
We're naughty crabs.
Pinch. Pinch. Pinch.
[GIGGLES]
Help! There are two naughty
crabs trying to pinch me!
Pinch. Pinch. Pinch.
We're naughty crabs.
[ALL LAUGH]
Shoo, shoo, shoo,
you naughty crabs.
Go back to your little
rock pools.
Yes.
[SNORTS]
Let's look in more
rock pools.
[SNORTING]
What can you see?
A seashell.
Can you hear the sea
in it?
What do you mean?
If you put a shell
to your ear,
you can hear the sea.
[SOUND OF CRASHING WAVES]
Wow.
I can hear the sea.
[SOUND OF CRASHING WAVES
RESUMES]
[GIGGLES]
I love my seashell.
George, can you find
a seashell too?
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
Shell!
[SNORTS]
That's not a shell.
Oh.
GRANDPA PIG:
Peppa's right.
That's not a shell.
George has found
a fossil.
What's a fossil?
GRANDPA PIG:
A fossil is the remains
of an animal that lived long
ago, when there were dinosaurs.
[SNORTING]
Dinosaur. Grrr.
[SQUEALS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Rock pools are such fun.
Yes, they're fun for us
but not for this little fish.
A fish? Where?
Ooh.
Poor little fish.
She's trapped.
Oh.
Oh?
The little fish says she wants
to go back to the sea.
Maybe you could use
your bucket to rescue her.
PEPPA:
Yes.
Peppa is rescuing
the little fish in her bucket.
Don't worry, Mrs. Fish.
You'll soon be back
with your friends.
[SNORTS]
Bye-bye, Mrs. Fish.
Bye-bye.
[LAUGHS]
ALL:
Oh!
[ALL LAUGH]
I love rock pools.
[ALL LAUGHING]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
NARRATOR:
Mr. Bull, the binman,
is collecting
the rubbish.
It is early morning,
so Mr. Bull tries to be
as quiet as he can.
[CANS CLATTERING LOUDLY]
But Mr. Bull is not very good
at being quiet.
Peppa and George
are finishing their breakfast.
[SNORTS]
What's that noise?
It's Mr. Bull, the binman.
[SNORTS]
Hello, Mr. Bull.
Moo!
Hello, everyone.
Must be off.
Lots of rubbish to collect.
ALL: Bye!
[COUGHS] Bye.
Moo!
Mr. Bull has emptied
the rubbish bin for us.
Good. Let's clear up
the breakfast things.
Can we help, Mommy?
Yes, you can.
Let's throw this empty bottle
in the bin.
Peppa, stop.
What?
We don't put bottles
in the rubbish bin.
They can be recycled.
What does that mean?
All the things
we can't use again
we put in the rubbish bin
for Mr. Bull.
But all the things
that can be used again
are put in these
recycle boxes.
DADDY PIG:
The red one is for newspapers,
the blue one is for tin cans
and the green one
is for bottles.
Peppa, you have a bottle.
So which box
does it go in?
Um, the green one.
MOMMY PIG:
Yes.
[GIGGLING]
This is fun.
Now it's George's turn.
Can you find a newspaper
for the red box?
[SNORTS AND GIGGLES]
George wants to recycle
Daddy Pig's newspaper.
[LAUGHING]
I haven't finished
with my newspaper
just yet, George.
You can have it
in a minute.
[SNORTS]
Oh, all right.
Here you are, George.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Newspapers go
in the red box, George.
[SNORTS]
[BOTH LAUGH]
Now that we have
collected enough things,
we can go
to the recycle center.
Hooray. Let's go.
Mommy Pig has the bottles...
[CLANKING]
...Peppa has the tin cans...
[RATTLING]
...and George has
the newspapers.
[RUFFLING]
Is everybody ready?
ALL:
Yes, Daddy Pig.
Then let's go.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
[RUBBISH RATTLING]
♪ Recycle, recycle
We're going to recycle ♪
♪ Tin cans ♪
[RATTLING]
♪ Bottles ♪
[CLANKING]
Newspapers.
[RUSTLING]
[RUBBISH RATTLING]
[LAUGHS]
♪ Recycle, recycle
We're going to recycle ♪
[ALL LAUGH]
This is Miss Rabbit's
recycle center.
We're here.
ALL: Hooray.
Hello, there.
Hello, Miss Rabbit.
Have you come to do
some recycling?
Yes, we have.
Jolly good.
[LIFT BEEPING]
Carry on.
PEPPA:
What's Miss Rabbit doing?
DADDY PIG:
She's recycling
all the rusty,
old cars.
PEPPA:
Wow!
Who can tell me which bin
the bottles go in?
The green one.
That's right.
[GLASS CLANKING]
And the cans
go in the blue one.
Well done, Peppa.
[RATTLING]
[SNORTS]
George wants to recycle
the newspapers.
Okay, George, you can do
[GIGGLES]
[ALL LAUGH]
There.
That's enough
recycling for one day.
Yes, let's go home.
[LAUGHING]
Oh, where's our car gone?
Peppa's car
has disappeared.
Stand back!
Miss Rabbit is recycling
Peppa's car.
[ALL GASP]
Stop!
That's our car!
What? Is it really?
ALL:
Yes!
Our car isn't
old and rusty.
[LAUGHS]
Silly me.
I just love recycling.
Yes. So do we.
But we also love
little our car.
Yes, and our little car
loves us too.
Don't you?
[HORN HONKS]
[ALL LAUGH]
[PEPPA READING ONSCREEN TEXT]
[DUCKS QUACKING]
NARRATOR:
The ducks are swimming
in their pond.
They are very happy.
Here are Peppa, George,
Mommy Pig and Daddy Pig.
Hello, ducks.
[QUACKING]
The ducks want some bread.
Sorry, Mrs. Duck,
we haven't got any bread today.
We've got something
much more fun.
Peppa has brought
her toy boat.
[QUACKING]
[SNORTS]
And George has brought
his toy boat.
Let's wind your boat up,
George.
George's boat
works with clockwork.
Quick, George,
put the boat in the pond
before the clockwork
runs out.
[GIGGLES]
[SNORTING]
George loves his
clockwork boat.
Mommy, can you wind
my boat up?
Your boat doesn't need
winding up, Peppa.
Peppa's boat is a sailboat.
The wind makes it go along.
I don't like my boat.
[SNORTS]
It doesn't do anything.
That's because there isn't
any wind today.
Maybe it just needs
a little help.
I'll huff and I'll puff
and I'll blow
your boat along.
[INHALING AND BLOWING]
[LAUGHING]
Hooray!
It went really fast.
Peppa loves her sailboat.
[BLEATING]
Here is Peppa's friend,
Suzy Sheep.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Suzy.
We're playing
with our boats.
[BLEATS]
I've got my speedboat.
Is it clockwork?
No. It has batteries.
Suzy's speedboat uses batteries
to make it go.
Ooh.
What a great speedboat.
[QUACKS]
Sorry, Mrs. Duck.
[QUACKING]
[BARKING]
Here is Danny Dog
with Granddad Dog.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Danny.
My Granddad has made me
this paddleboat.
ALL:
Ooh.
I say.
That's impressive.
[SNORTS]
How does it work?
It's steam-powered.
I just push
this little lever.
[TOOTS]
ALL:
Wow.
What a fantastic
paddleboat.
[QUACKING]
[SQUEAKING]
Here is Rebecca Rabbit
with her mommy.
Hello, everyone.
Hello, Rebecca.
We're playing
with our boats.
I wish I had a boat.
Rebecca Rabbit
does not have a boat.
I've got an idea.
Luckily I brought
my newspaper along.
I just need one page.
Which page can we lose?
News? Sport?
Ah, fashion.
Not the fashion page.
Okay, I'll use
the business page.
When I was
a little piggy,
I used to fold newspaper
like this.
What is Daddy Pig doing?
To make a paper boat.
Daddy Pig has made
a paper boat.
[SQUEAKS]
Thank you, Mr. Pig.
[CHUCKLES]
[SNORTS]
George wants
a paper boat too.
[DADDY PIG LAUGHS]
I suppose I can do
without the sports page.
[SNORTS AND LAUGHS]
Please can I have one?
And me.
[LAUGHS]
Of course.
Daddy Pig is making
paper boats for everyone.
Let's have a race.
Good idea, Mommy Pig.
We can huff and puff
and blow the paper boats across.
Everyone take
a deep breath.
[ALL INHALE]
Ready? Steady?
Blow!
[ALL BLOWING]
We have a winner.
Uh, who had
the sports page?
That's George's boat.
George is the winner.
ALL:
Hooray!
[ALL GIGGLE]
I like boats.
And I like
paper boats the best.
ALL:
Me too!
[ALL LAUGH]
It's time to go home.
Everybody has had
a great time.
ALL:
Bye-bye!
Bye-bye, ducks.
See you soon.
The ducks enjoyed
the toy boats.
But they quite like
having the pond
back to themselves again.
[QUACKING]
[PEPPA LAUGHING AND SNORTING]
♪ Peppa Pig ♪
[SNORTING AND LAUGHING]